{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1410,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":10,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz --Shopping Safetly-- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1. If Santa’s elves are busy and Santa decided to get the gifts using online shopping, is it best for Santa to use the web browser on a mobile device or the web browser on a home computer? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Mobile Device is safer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mobile Device is safer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Home computer is safer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Home computer is safer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24884","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"They are both equal ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24884_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They are both equal\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Scammers use fake URLs similar to those of legitimate retailers, knowing that URLs don’t show up as well in a smaller mobile web browser address field. It is also easier for scammers to insert phishing links that look more convenient for the user into smaller web browser pages.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  Scammers use fake URLs similar to those of legitimate retailers, knowing that URLs don’t show up as well in a smaller mobile web browser address field. It is also easier for scammers to insert phishing links that look more convenient for the user into smaller web browser pages.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si24888","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. If Santa’s elves are busy and Santa decided to get the gifts using online shopping, is it best for Santa to use the web browser on a mobile device or the web browser on a home computer?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2. When online shopping we can visit websites that are spoofed. Spoofing can be described as which of the following? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"Eavesdropping on a communication link ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eavesdropping on a communication link\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"Pretending to be someone or something else ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pretending to be someone or something else\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Working through a list of words ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Working through a list of words\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Session hijacking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24752_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Session hijacking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24899","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24903","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A snowball fight ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24899_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A snowball fight\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer: B  You might find yourself dealing with fraudulent ecommerce sites that take your money – and run. Criminals behind ecommerce scams create fake sites intended to spoof -- or look identical to -- the real thing.  Before you know it, you're making a payment to a criminal out to steal your money. Always confirm that you are using the correct site or the correct app when shopping online.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  You might find yourself dealing with fraudulent ecommerce sites that take your money – and run. Criminals behind ecommerce scams create fake sites intended to spoof -- or look identical to -- the real thing.  Before you know it, you're making a payment to a criminal out to steal your money. Always confirm that you are using the correct site or the correct app when shopping online.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si24741","si24756","si24903","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. When online shopping we can visit websites that are spoofed. Spoofing can be described as which of the following?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3. The winter months bring out the generosity of the public and many want to donate to a charity. Scammers know this and will set up fake charity scams to get your money.  True or False? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  The Better Business Bureau advises that people wishing to donate to a charity can check out its validity at http://www.give.org (or your local BBB) before donating. Use the internet to do some research on the charity and the safest method of giving money. Then feel good about it.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  A  The Better Business Bureau advises that people wishing to donate to a charity can check out its validity at http://www.give.org (or your local BBB) before donating. Use the internet to do some research on the charity and the safest method of giving money. Then feel good about it.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. The winter months bring out the generosity of the public and many want to donate to a charity. Scammers know this and will set up fake charity scams to get your money.  True or False?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. If we are making new accounts for online shopping, what is the most important advice to always follow regarding passwords? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"Different password for each account ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Different password for each account\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"Make passwords long ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Make passwords long\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"Combine upper and lower case ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Combine upper and lower case\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Include numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Include numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24918","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Always use the word Elves in your password ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24914_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Always use the word Elves in your password\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Every day, online accounts are breached, with user names and passwords sold on the dark web. A threat actor who gets your user name and password for one account will try it for numerous others because they count on the fact that people use the same password for multiple accounts.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  A  Every day, online accounts are breached, with user names and passwords sold on the dark web. A threat actor who gets your user name and password for one account will try it for numerous others because they count on the fact that people use the same password for multiple accounts.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si24918","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. If we are making new accounts for online shopping, what is the most important advice to always follow regarding passwords?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  If you think that you may have been compromised while online shopping, what is the easiest method to learn if someone has made fraudulent charges on your bank or credit card accounts? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"Wait until your card is rejected ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_403","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wait until your card is rejected\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"Check the transactions regularly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_404","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check the transactions regularly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Wait until the bank contacts you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_405","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wait until the bank contacts you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23085","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"Send a letter to Santa and ask for help ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"406","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Send a letter to Santa and ask for help\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  It is best if you can detect and report any fraud on your account as quickly as possible. You should check the transactions on your accounts regularly – by receiving statements, by using the ATM, by setting up telephone banking to get your balance and transactions, or via online banking. Many people rely solely on their cards, so it is important to know they are safe.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  It is best if you can detect and report any fraud on your account as quickly as possible. You should check the transactions on your accounts regularly – by receiving statements, by using the ATM, by setting up telephone banking to get your balance and transactions, or via online banking. Many people rely solely on their cards, so it is important to know they are safe.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23078","si23089","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  If you think that you may have been compromised while online shopping, what is the easiest method to learn if someone has made fraudulent charges on your bank or credit card accounts?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  If you decide to perform your Christmas shopping online, what is the most important thing you need to do? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"Bake Christmas cookies in case you get hungry ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bake Christmas cookies in case you get hungry\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"Ensure a secure connection ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure a secure connection\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24779","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Avoid suspicious looking people and grinches  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24779_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Avoid suspicious looking people and grinches \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24794","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Bring extra eggnog ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24794_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bring extra eggnog\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Avoid using public Wi-Fi.  It is better to use your cellular data plan than the local restaurant’s Wi-Fi. You can download a VPN (Virtual Private Network) app for free from your official app store for private web use. Make sure the shopping site uses HTTPS, not HTTP, and the lock symbol. (Buying your favourite beverage and avoiding suspicious looking people are always good advice.)  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  Avoid using public Wi-Fi.  It is better to use your cellular data plan than the local restaurant’s Wi-Fi. You can download a VPN (Virtual Private Network) app for free from your official app store for private web use. Make sure the shopping site uses HTTPS, not HTTP, and the lock symbol. (Buying your favourite beverage and avoiding suspicious looking people are always good advice.)  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si24783","si24798","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  If you decide to perform your Christmas shopping online, what is the most important thing you need to do?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  Phishing attacks are rampant because they work!  How do phishers snare online shoppers? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"Scaring you. “If you don’t pay the CRA, you will be added to Santa’s naughty list!” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Scaring you. “If you don’t pay the CRA, you will be added to Santa’s naughty list!”\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"Offering huge discounts. “20% off holidays to the north pole” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_412","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Offering huge discounts. “20% off holidays to the north pole”\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"Offering great opportunities. “Earn 100,000 a year working in Santa’s workshop” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_413","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Offering great opportunities. “Earn 100,000 a year working in Santa’s workshop”\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Phishers design their campaigns to play on human nature : the tendency to trust; being in a hurry; not reading details; and fear of missing out on a special offer or on an undesirable event like an account being closed.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  D  Phishers design their campaigns to play on human nature : the tendency to trust; being in a hurry; not reading details; and fear of missing out on a special offer or on an undesirable event like an account being closed.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  Phishing attacks are rampant because they work!  How do phishers snare online shoppers?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_198","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298","Image_198"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Dec2019Quiz","class":"project","title":"Dec2019Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":70,"passScore":56}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 10"}]}